Hello friends, today we are going to read the
results of the fourth quarter of the final year 2021 of ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Limited, that is, the March quarter. So let's start with the
board announcing a dividend of ₹5 per equity share in its meeting. Let's
read the company's last quarter statement and find out that the
company has made a profit. This is the last time
I have worked out the profit and loss treatment of the company.
Here, all the A's are in Great Lakes. First of all,
we will see the total income. The
total income in this company is Rs
4634, which is Rs 50,814 lakh in the December quarter
and Rs
3,48,90,39 lakh in the March quarter of the previous financial year. The
total income of the previous financial year was Rs
12,137 lakh and the total income in this financial year is Rs
16,12,988. On comparing this, it is
found that the total income on a quarter-on-quarter basis is Rs
20.365 lakh and this is on an annual basis.
On checking the total income of 32.90, it is found that
on the basis of quarter on point, the total income has
increased by 20.3 percent and on the basis of this and this, the
total income is increased by 22.91. If we
compare the financial year with the
previous financial year, then the
total income has increased by 32.96 in this financial year.
Now we will see from the total expenses, the total
expenses in the March quarter seemed to be 3 lakh
62 thousand 670, in the December quarter it was
3 lakh 58 thousand 107 and
in the March quarter of the previous financial year it
seemed to be 2 lakh 70 thousand 751.
It is found that
on the basis of quarter on point, the total
expenses have increased by 1.3 percent and
on the basis of this and this, the total expenses are
more than 34.08. If we
compile the data of a pan share, then the
net expenses in the last financial year were
10 lakh  20 thousand 506 and
net expenses in this financial year stood at 14 lakh 33 thousand 591
which shows an increase of 20.47 percent.
Now let's move on to total profit i.e. net
comprehensive income. Net companies are
looking at 1251 in the quarter and 1753 in the December quarter.
In terms of likes and shares, it is
34567 lakh two,
so here the profit has
decreased by 1.6 verses on the basis of coffee powder and this and this has
decreased by 96% on the basis of
last financial year's net profit was 1 lakh
47 thousand 305 lakh and this financial year
's net profit was 1 lakh 27 thousand one hundred one,
so this is the total profit on the basis of on air, a
decrease of 31.72 percent has been
seen. Let's
look at Yo Yo Honey,
in the marks quarter, GPS is 6.7 percent and in the December
quarter  In the quarter it was 6.47 percent and in the last financial quarter it was
7.6 percent. Here I
subtract GPS from 1.5
and this is UP from 6.3 percent
and the history of the last financial year was 32.41
percent which has come back to 25.91 in this financial year
and if we look at it financial year
wise then
GPS is down from 20.06 percent. Margin has
run from 1 point to 20% in this quarter which was 1
point to 4% in the December quarter and in the
last financial year it was
986 percent. We can see that we have seen a decline in the mosque.
So let's see the
effect of the company's profit loss on the share price. You can see that due to the company's net
profit going home from 9.6 percent, there has been a
decline of 5.7 percent in the share price in intraday. The insurance
sector is a good group tractor market
in India. Ad General Insurance which
improves the duty point ranger products
that its accused
70% and the accused is a typical 1.3% and the debt
to equity ratio is 50 which
indicates good fundamentals. If we
ignore the decline in short profits and
try to take a long-term view,
then a good wine
opportunity can be seen here
because the stock price is trading at a discount of 21.3% from its all-time high.
What is your opinion on this? Please write in the comment box.
If you liked this Anil Sais, then do
share it with others and
like the video. Don't forget to subscribe to the channel and
press the bell icon button so that I can keep
bringing more such videos for Elizabeth.
Thank you. Have a good day. Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal